Pido disculpas por el retraso.
Everything will be resolved shortly.
You will receive your purchased lot.
Okay.
Listen,
the cops are here,
right outside in the hallway.
So?
They're asking about your paintings.
What?
Listen, we have to move.
Now.
No, Anthony.
Listen, I'm not going anywhere, okay?
You will!
Miss Aspen,
please remain where you are.
You are under arrest
on suspicion of involvement
in international drug trafficking.
What?
What? Officer?
Listen, this is some kind of
misunderstanding.
I'm sure of that.
Ma'am, please,
just keep your hands
where I can see them.
Officer, listen.
You got the wrong person.
I'm telling you, she's innocent.
Hey!
You can't just arrest people like that.
Yes, we can.